https://www.cornelius.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.TopicsWho we areWhat information do we collect about you?How we will use the information collectedWith whom do we share the information collectedMarketingAccess to your information and correctionsCookiesOther websitesChanges to our privacy policyHow to contact usWho we areCornelius (Cornelius Group plc) are a specialty chemical distributor headquartered in Bishop’s Stortford, Hertfordshire. We are a group of companies that include:Cornelius Group plcCornelius Specialties LtdCornelius Polska Sp z. o. o.What information do we collect about you?Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified.We collect personal information about you when you voluntarily complete the Contact Us page to allow us to answer your query. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions.Website usage information is collected using cookies.How we will use the information collectedWe may use your personal information to:Improve our products and your experience on the Cornelius websitesTo contact you regarding products and services which may be of legitimate interest to you, provided you have given us consent to do so or you have previously requested a product or service from us and the communication is relevant or related to that prior request and made within any timeframes established by applicable lawsTo provide you with products or services that you request from usWith whom do we share the information collectedWe may share your personal information with:Our advertising, marketing and promotional agencies to help us deliver and analyse the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns and promotionsThird parties required to deliver a product or service to you, such as a delivery or postal service delivering a product that you have orderedLaw enforcement or government authorities where they have followed due legal process to request us to disclose the informationIf we do share your personal information with another Cornelius Group company or with trusted third parties, we shall use our best efforts to ensure that they keep your information secure, take all reasonable steps to protect it from misuse and only use it in a manner consistent with our instructions, this Privacy Notice and applicable data protection laws and regulations.MarketingWe would like to send you information about products and services of ours and other companies within our group which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at any time.We will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose.You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving information to other members of the Cornelius Group.If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, email or write to us at the following address.Access to your information and correctionsYou have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email or write to us at the following address. We may make a small charge for this service.We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate. Please email or write to us at the following address.CookiesWe use cookies on our website for a variety of reasons which you can learn about below. The cookies we use do not store personally identifiable information nor can they harm your computer. We want our website to be informative, personal, and as user friendly as possible and cookies help us to achieve that goal.Our use of cookies is explained fully on our Cookies Policy pageOther websitesOur website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website, so when you click a link to another website you should read their own privacy policies.Changes to our privacy policyWe perform regular reviews of our privacy policy and update appropriately. This privacy policy was last updated 06/02/2018How to contact usPlease contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:By emailBy writing to us at the following address
Any questions? Get in touch today!
Contact us
Emergency 24/7
Carechem Hotline
For chemical spills and emergencies, please telephone the Cornelius Carechem Hotline:
+44 (0) 1235 239 670
Please note: For emergency use only.
© 2020 Cornelius, All rights reserved.
Design by phd.
